{"data":[{"question":"He returned money to the man who ________ it.","a":"loose","b":"have lost","c":"lost","d":"had lost","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Past perfect tense: expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past (returned).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"The film didn't ________ to our expectations.","a":"equal","b":"give","c":"equally","d":"gave","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Equal to: to be as good as something else, or get to the same standard as someone or something else.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"There are three categories ________ answers you can choose one.","a":"of","b":"about","c":"with","d":"in","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Category of: a group of people or things that are all of the same type.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Children with ________ faces waiting for the pantomime to start.","a":"expectant","b":"expected","c":"expect","d":"expectation","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Preposition (by, of, in, on...) + Verb_ing\/noun\/noun phrase (adj + noun).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Those fellows seem dull and I want to get ________ of them quickly.","a":"pant","b":"rid","c":"chance","d":"difficult","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Get rid of sbd\/sth: to throw away or destroy something you do not want any more.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"The suggestions above are just some of the ways to increase your ________ awareness.","a":"culture","b":"culturally","c":"cultural","d":"cultured","answer":"3","explain":"\n- We use possessive adjectives to show who owns or \"possesses\" something. The possessive adjectives are : my, your, his,her, its, our, their, whose .\n+ My, your, his,her, its, our, their, whose + Noun\/noun phrase (Adj+ noun).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"My roommates ________ dinner by the time I got home.","a":"finished","b":"finish","c":"had finished","d":"have finished","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Clause (past perfect) + by the time + past simple\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"We express our thoughts by means ________ word.","a":"in","b":"to","c":"on","d":"of","answer":"4","explain":"\n- By means of: using a particular method or system of doing something","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"The witness's account was not ________ with the facts.","a":"match","b":"reliable","c":"consistent","d":"confirmed","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Consistent with: if a fact, idea etc is consistent with another one, it seems to match it.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"It was not until she had arrived home ________ remembered her appointment with the doctor.","a":"when she","b":"that she","c":"and she","d":"she","answer":"2","explain":"\n- (not) until ... that + clause (past simple)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"}]}